keep your heart in tip-top shape with
these cardio workouts tina's joined by a
tone and sculpt coach who i guarantee
can open up a jar of pickles like
nobody's business tina just by blinking
like this
right melissa keptner how you doing
melissa i am doing well how are you guys
doing pretty good
you're in philadelphia right
yes at bucks county pennsylvania so
right outside philadelphia wonderful
county there you go okay so first off
just quickly tell us what tone and
sculpt is i know it's an app right
yes turn and sculpt is truly a fitness
for all apps we have varying different
workout programs guided workout programs
on there um on on-demand classes okay i
lead on-demand classes i leave guided
running workouts there's recipes it's
truly a one-stop shop fitness for all
apps it's women run right
yes 100
okay so today world heart day and you
tell us
why it's so important to get up offers
chairs and the couches to move
it is a movement is so crucial to do on
a daily basis i truly made it a mission
to educate and encourage all around the
world to get up and move
because our bodies want to move crave to
move and need to move i like to tell
people that
sitting in a static position
um really that's when all the aches and
pains start that's when we get that bad
posture so when we get up and move on a
regular basis it improves our physical
well-being it helps manage chronic
conditions um it improves our longevity
our quality of life our bone density and
it also can improve our mood as well yes
okay give us something to start off with
for those of us that are a little on the
lazy side what can we just start off
with just to get not so overwhelmed
yeah you just want to start small that's
what i always like to say and i have
just a few moves here that you can do in
the comfort of your own home okay that
you can do while you're at work so i can
demo them if you'd like okay go ahead go
ahead we got about a minute we're gonna
get up we're gonna get up and move so
the one exercise you want to get your
whole body involved so we're gonna do
overhead reaches you're watching netflix
you get up and you just do 30 seconds
reaching all the way overhead and
extending your leg
so these are no excuse movement oh
everybody's doing it here
yeah you're not jumping you're keeping
your core tight and you're just reaching
and extending your leg
and the second movement to do right
after that is you squat down
and come up onto your toes so we're
getting a little bit of balance involved
squatting down coming up onto your toes
yes wonderful if we have time for one
more exercise go ahead go ahead
elevated mountain climbers so we're not
going to get on the floor you find a
sturdy table
or a chair you get into a high plank
position your your core is tight and you
drive your knees into your chest you can
go nice and slow and then once you feel
comfortable you can speed it up and jog
it out oh
these are no excuse movements we don't
need weight we're elevating our heart
rate we're getting our whole entire body
involved
and that is what it's all about it's
about building routine it's about just
finding efficient effective and fun
movement so commercial breaks we gotta
move we gotta move
yeah all right how do people get in
touch with you or sign up
yes uh you can go to the tony sculpt app
in the app store you can find me on
instagram at melissa underscore kendra
um and we're constantly running
challenges we constantly have new styles
coming out so it's absolutely amazing
well thank you for your time on this day
world heart day let's get our hearts
going everybody
all right longevity yes all right back
over to you thank you